marksdailyapple.com 2007-12-14

# Mark’s Daily Apple » Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

**Mark’s Daily Apple Blog & Forum Privacy Policy**

_Mark’s Daily Apple_ believes that your privacy is very important. Read the following to learn all about our privacy policy.

Our policy applies to all personal information given and received, including all information from your past use of any of our products and services. We define personal information as anything that would identify you: your address, your phone and email contact information, your name, your preferences, and other information that is not generally available to the public. Of course, this policy applies to _Mark’s Daily Apple_ and no other companies or entities.

_Mark’s Daily Apple_ does gather personal information about you when you register, use any of our products and services, or visit any of our pages or pages of our partners. We may combine information about you with information from other associates and partners.

When you become a member, we collect information about you such as your name, contact information, birth date, gender, location, occupation, and preferences. For purchases and some services we may ask for your social security number and relevant financial information. Once you join, we know you – you are not anonymous. We collect information about your interactions with us and our partners. We do this automatically. Your browser also gives us your IP address and cookie information.

What we do with this information: We do this to personalize your experience – nothing more, nothing less. This information allows us to fulfill your requests for our products and services, talk to you, improve our service to you, and provide strictly anonymous reporting to other clients.

Children under 13 must have a parent or guardian approve registry with _Mark’s Daily Apple_. We will not contact children under 13 for personal information, sales promotions, or marketing purposes.

We don’t rent, sell, give or share any of your personal information unless it’s to provide a service or product you request or is regulated by confidential requirements. We value our relationship with you and we value your privacy. Your information is never made available without your explicit consent.

_Mark’s Daily Apple_ may need to set a cookie on your computer. Other companies that are not affiliated with _Mark’s Daily Apple_ do not have access to our cookies.

You can edit your profile, preferences and settings at any time.

We reserve the right to talk to you about matters related to your use of products and services associated with _Mark’s Daily Apple_ , including but not limited to announcements, service and administrative updates, and health information.

You are always free to terminate your membership with _Mark’s Daily Apple_.

We provide complete physical, electronic and procedural security steps that comply with all federal government regulations in order to protect your information. We do not share your information with employees without their demonstrated, reasonable need to access your information in order to perform their jobs related to providing you with products and services that you request.

From time to time, we may modify our policy. We will always inform you of any changes by contacting you via the email address you have given us.

If you have any questions, please feel free to ask us by shooting us a line on the forum.

**Disclaimer:** Views expressed on this website are just that - views. Opinions and information presented on this site are not intended to replace the advice of your primary health care provider.  Please enjoy responsibly!
